<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Branding on Chris Bennett</title>
    <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/tags/branding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Branding on Chris Bennett</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.chrisbennett.io/tags/branding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Louisville Jefferson County Information Consortium</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/lojic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/lojic/</guid>
      <description>LOJIC (The Louisville / Jefferson County Information Consortium) is a multi-agency partnership that builds and maintains a Geographic Information System to serve Louisville, KY, and the surrounding county. Or, in more plain language, they make maps and mapping services – both digital and print.
I was tasked with redesigning their aging site. The goals and objectives? Make it look better. Ok, not the most specific set of constraints, but you make do with what you have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harbor Media</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/harbor-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/harbor-media/</guid>
      <description>I teamed up with Mike Cosper to work on branding for a new non-profit media company he was starting, Harbor Media. Mike loves vintage audio gear and classic broadcasting branding, but the first thing his new organization was going to do was produce podcasts. The first challenge was how to combine the aesthetic of classic American broadcasting branding with the more recent medium of podcasting.
Inspiration Our initial inspiration came from the vintage logos of companies like RCA, NBC, and the National Radio Service Men&amp;rsquo;s Association:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King’s Cross Church</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/kings-cross-church/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/kings-cross-church/</guid>
      <description>I love working with non-profits. They often have limited resources, but make up for it with passion, vision, and scrappiness. These kinds of constraints often produce the best results, as they force an expedient focus on no-nonsense, direct results. They don&amp;rsquo;t have time, or the money, to waste.
King’s Cross Church is a church plant in San Francisco, CA. Being in a city known for being at the forefront of technological innovation, they wanted something clean, simple, and straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>