<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Chris Bennett</title>
    <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Chris Bennett</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.chrisbennett.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Covenant Eyes</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/covenant-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/covenant-eyes/</guid>
      <description>I am a designer with more than a decade of experience crafting solutions in a variety of contexts – from local churches to Fortune 500 companies. About 10 years ago I used Covenant Eyes for the first time, and since then I&#39;ve watched from a distance as you and the team stick to your mission while continuing to improve the product. Now, I&#39;d like to join you in that work!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gethsemani Farms</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/ora-et-labora/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/ora-et-labora/</guid>
      <description>In 1848, 44 Roman Catholic Trappist monks established the Abbey of Gethsemani in Kentucky. The Order of Cistercians of the Strict Observance follow the Rule of St. Benedict, focusing on peace, work, and prayer. Originally supporting themselves through farming, the monks now sell homemade fruitcakes, fudge, and more. Despite having the best bourbon fudge around,1 they needed help to make it a bit easier for their customers to buy more of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design of Project for Client</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/cya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/cya/</guid>
      <description>Some of my work lives behind an NDA, or some other form of agreement that says I can&amp;rsquo;t show it to you. Bummer. So, in place of that work, here is a choose your own adventure of how some of that work may have gone.1
The Start You sit alone at your desk. You gaze into the radiating glow of your monitor, waiting for inspiration. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t show up. A feeling of unease creeps into your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louisville Jefferson County Information Consortium</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/lojic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/lojic/</guid>
      <description>LOJIC (The Louisville / Jefferson County Information Consortium) is a multi-agency partnership that builds and maintains a Geographic Information System to serve Louisville, KY, and the surrounding county. Or, in more plain language, they make maps and mapping services – both digital and print.
I was tasked with redesigning their aging site. The goals and objectives? Make it look better. Ok, not the most specific set of constraints, but you make do with what you have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSD</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/msd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/msd/</guid>
      <description>The Louisville / Jefferson County Metropolitan Sewer District (MSD) had an old site. Really old – Clinton is president, we are prepping for Y2K, and Napster is about to drop – old. Quick confession: I actually liked their old site. What it lacked in visual interest it made up for in obviousness. And, it had a Space Jam meets your public utility company vibe that is missing from the web these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harbor Media</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/harbor-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/harbor-media/</guid>
      <description>I teamed up with Mike Cosper to work on branding for a new non-profit media company he was starting, Harbor Media. Mike loves vintage audio gear and classic broadcasting branding, but the first thing his new organization was going to do was produce podcasts. The first challenge was how to combine the aesthetic of classic American broadcasting branding with the more recent medium of podcasting.
Inspiration Our initial inspiration came from the vintage logos of companies like RCA, NBC, and the National Radio Service Men&amp;rsquo;s Association:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King’s Cross Church</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/kings-cross-church/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/kings-cross-church/</guid>
      <description>I love working with non-profits. They often have limited resources, but make up for it with passion, vision, and scrappiness. These kinds of constraints often produce the best results, as they force an expedient focus on no-nonsense, direct results. They don&amp;rsquo;t have time, or the money, to waste.
King’s Cross Church is a church plant in San Francisco, CA. Being in a city known for being at the forefront of technological innovation, they wanted something clean, simple, and straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Work</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisbennett.io/other-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisbennett.io/other-work/</guid>
      <description> Logo for Trinity Community Church  Album cover for Brooks Ritter, Stereo of Steel   Banner for Redemption Church Kids  Shirt design   Seed - logo for community redevelopment nonprofit  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>